好吧,你完成了。虽然以后还有很多新事情
All right, you're done. There were a lot of new things that time. But, afterall,
但是你成为一名经验丰富的Android程序员了
you're becoming a seasoned Android programmer by now.
我刚才提到，我们用NotificationCompat.Builder
As I mentioned before, we're going to use NotificationCompat.Builder
来创建一个Notification。它可以很容易的就
to build our notification. It's easy to build
建立一个漂亮的通知
a nice looking notification that has our icon
拥有图标和标题
representing the weather forecast, the title for our
以及文本内容
App. And our content text, the forecast with
还有高温和低温的预报。
highs and lows. We're going to use another class
我们再用支持库里的另外一个类为pending intent
from the support library, to create a task stack builder
创建一个taskStackBuilder。
for our pending intent. This is a simple case
这是一个taskStackBuilder的简单例子，因为
of task stack builder, because all we have is a
我们只有一个单独项。
single item on our stack. We just add the
只要添加nextIntent,并且用它创建出pending intent
next intent and use it to build out pending intent
再传入notificationManager里面就好了。
that we pass into the notification manager. Finally we call
最后调用notificationManager，它其中包含通过buidler所创建的intent对象
the notification manager with the built intent from our builder,
notificationManager很棒的一点是，它可以被用于任何线程
with a notify function. One of the great things about notification manager is
甚至是UI线程
it can be used from any thread even though it is displaying UI.